<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tim Balbalan</string>

    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munich FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <array name="club_detail">
        <item>Camp Nou (Catalan pronunciation: , \"new field\", often incorrectly referred to as the
            \"Nou Camp\" in English) is the home stadium of FC Barcelona since its completion in
            1957.\r\n\r\nWith a seating capacity of 99,354, it is the largest stadium in Spain and
            Europe, and the second largest association football stadium in the world in terms of
            capacity. It has hosted two European Cup/Champions League finals in 1989 and 1999, five
            matches including the opening game of the 1982 FIFA World Cup and the football
            competition final at the 1992 Summer Olympics.
        </item>
        <item>The Santiago Bernabéu Stadium (Spanish: Estadio Santiago Bernabéu ), is the home
            stadium of Real Madrid since its completion in 1947, with a current seating capacity of
            81,044.\r\n\r\nSantiago Bernabéu is one of the world's most famous and prestigious
            football venues. It has hosted the European Cup/Champions League final on four
            occasions: in 1957, 1969, 1980 and 2010. The final matches for the 1964 European
            Nations' Cup and the 1982 FIFA World Cup, were also held at the Bernabéu, thus making it
            the first stadium in Europe to host both a UEFA European Championship and a FIFA World
            Cup final.
        </item>
        <item>The Allianz Arena is a football stadium in Munich, Bavaria, Germany with a 75,024
            seating capacity. Widely known for its exterior of inflated ETFE plastic panels, it is
            the first stadium in the world with a full color-changing color exterior. Located at 25
            Werner-Heisenberg-Allee at the northern edge of Munich's Schwabing-Freimann borough on
            the Fröttmaning Heath, it is the third largest arena in Germany behind Signal Iduna Park
            in Dortmund and the Olympiastadion in Berlin.\r\n\r\nThe two professional Munich
            football clubs FC Bayern Munich and TSV 1860 München have played their home games at the
            Allianz Arena since the start of the 2005–06 season. The clubs had previously played
            their home games at the Munich Olympic Stadium since 1972. TSV 1860 München previously
            had a 50% share in the stadium but FC Bayern Munich purchased their shares for 11
            million euros in April, 2006. The arrangement allows TSV 1860 München to play at the
            stadium while retaining no ownership.\r\n\r\nThe large financial services provider
            Allianz purchased the naming rights to the stadium for 30 years. However this name
            cannot be used when hosting FIFA and UEFA events, since these governing bodies have
            policies forbidding corporate sponsorship from companies that are not official
            tournament partners. During the 2006 World Cup, the stadium was referred to as FIFA
            World Cup Stadium Munich. In UEFA club matches, it is known as Fußball Arena München
            (Football Arena Munich) , and it hosted the 2012 UEFA Champions League Final. The
            stadium has been nicknamed \"Schlauchboot\" (inflatable boat). The museum of Bayern
            Munich, FC Bayern Erlebniswelt, is located inside the Allianz Arena.
        </item>
        <item>The City of Manchester Stadium in Manchester, England, also known as Etihad Stadium
            for
            sponsorship reasons, is the home ground of Manchester City Football Club. For the
            2014/15 football season, the stadium has a reduced capacity of 45,500 due to expansion
            work. Capacity will increase to 62,000 from August 2015 making it the second-largest
            stadium in the Premier League and the ninth-largest in the United Kingdom.\r\n\r\nThe
            SportCity location, but with a larger stadium, had been proposed for the main athletics
            arena in Manchester's failed bid for the 2000 Summer Olympics. In the 2002 Commonwealth
            Games bid, the capacity for the Games was to be 38,000, and after the games it would be
            converted to be 48,000. The stadium was built by Laing Construction at a cost of £112
            million and was designed and engineered by ArupSport. The design incorporated a highly
            complex yet elegant cable-stayed roof structure which is suspended by twelve exterior
            masts and attached cables.\r\n\r\nTo ensure the long-term future of the stadium after
            the Commonwealth Games, it was agreed in 1998 that Manchester City F.C. would lease the
            stadium from Manchester City Council as a replacement for Maine Road. The conversion
            from a track and field arena to a football stadium cost the city council £22 million and
            Manchester City £20 million The club moved into its new home during the summer of
            2003.\r\n\r\nIn addition to athletics, the stadium has hosted the 2008 UEFA Cup Final,
            England football internationals, rugby league matches, boxing world title fights and
            music concerts, and will host one 2015 Rugby World Cup match.\r\n\r\nIn March 2014 work
            commenced on expansion with the south stand roof partially removed over the summer to
            allow construction to take place. The work is due to be completed by the beginning of
            the 2015/16 football season with capacity increasing to over 55,000. The expansion will
            coincide with development immediately adjacent to the stadium and the completion of the
            Etihad Campus training facility, Connell Sixth Form College and community hub which is
            partly funded by Manchester City.
        </item>
        <item>Old Trafford is a football stadium in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England, and
            the home of Manchester United F.C. With a capacity of 75,635, Old Trafford is the
            second-largest football stadium in the United Kingdom after Wembley Stadium, and the
            ninth-largest in Europe. It is about 0.5 miles (800 m) from Old Trafford Cricket Ground
            and the adjacent tram station.\r\n\r\nOld Trafford, nicknamed the Theatre of Dreams by
            Bobby Charlton, has been United's home ground since 1910, although from 1941 to 1949, as
            a result of bomb damage during the Second World War, the club shared Maine Road with
            local rivals Manchester City. Old Trafford underwent several expansions in the 1990s and
            2000s, including the addition of extra tiers to the North, West and East Stands, which
            served to return the ground almost to its original capacity of 80,000. Future expansion
            is likely to involve the addition of a second tier to the South Stand, which would raise
            the capacity to over 90,000. The stadium's record attendance was recorded in 1939, when
            76,962 spectators watched the FA Cup semi-final between Wolverhampton Wanderers and
            Grimsby Town.\r\n\r\nOld Trafford has hosted FA Cup semi-finals, England fixtures,
            matches at the 1966 World Cup and Euro 96 and the 2003 Champions League Final, as well
            as rugby league's annual Super League Grand Final and the final of two Rugby League
            World Cups. It also hosted football matches at the 2012 Summer Olympics, including
            women's international football for the first time in its history.
        </item>
        <item>Stamford Bridge (/ˈstæm.fərd ˈbrɪdʒ/) is a football stadium located in Fulham, London.
            It is the home ground of Chelsea F.C.. The stadium is located within the Moore Park
            Estate also known as Walham Green and is often referred to as simply The Bridge. The
            capacity is 41,798, making it the eighth largest ground in the Premier
            League.\r\n\r\nOpened in 1877, the stadium was used by the London Athletic Club until
            1905, when new owner Gus Mears founded Chelsea Football Club to occupy the ground;
            Chelsea have played their home games there ever since. It has undergone numerous major
            changes over the years, most recently in the 1990s when it was renovated into a modern,
            all-seater stadium.\r\n\r\nStamford Bridge has been used as a venue for England
            international matches, FA Cup Finals, FA Cup semi-finals and Charity Shield games. It
            has also hosted numerous other sports, such as cricket, rugby union, speedway, greyhound
            racing, baseball and American football. The stadium's highest official attendance is
            82,905, for a league match between Chelsea and Arsenal on 12 October 1935.
        </item>
        <item>he Stadio Giuseppe Meazza, commonly known as San Siro, is a football stadium located
            in the San Siro district in Milan, Italy. It is the home of both A.C. Milan and F.C.
            Internazionale Milano. On 3 March 1980, the stadium was named in honour of Giuseppe
            Meazza, the two-time World Cup winner (1934, 1938) who played for Internazionale, and
            briefly for Milan, in the 1920s, 1930s and 1940s. It held UEFA five-star stadium status
            which was superseded by a new system of classification.
        </item>
        <item>The Emirates Stadium (known as Ashburton Grove prior to sponsorship) is a football
            stadium in Holloway, London, England, and the home of Arsenal Football Club. With a
            capacity of 60,272, the Emirates is the third-largest football stadium in England after
            Wembley and Old Trafford.In 1997, Arsenal explored the possibility of relocating to a
            new stadium, having been denied planning permission by Islington Council to expand its
            home ground of Highbury. After considering various options (including purchasing
            Wembley), the club bought an industrial and waste disposal estate in Ashburton Grove in
            2000. A year later they won the council's approval to build a stadium on the site;
            manager Arsène Wenger described this as the \"biggest decision in Arsenal's history\"
            since the board appointed Herbert Chapman. Relocation began in 2002, but financial
            difficulties delayed work until February 2004. Emirates Airline was later announced as
            the main sponsor for the stadium. Work was completed in 2006 at a cost of £390 million.
        </item>
    </array>
</resources>
